Guide to the James Beard Foundation Archive 1939-2008 (bulk 1990-2008) MSS.214
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Chefs
  - Britton, David, 2000-2003 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Broadbent, Michael, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Broadmoor Chefs, undated (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Broberg, Chris, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Broceaux, Victor, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Brock, Sean, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Brockman, J. Steven, 1995-2006 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Brodsky, Bill, 1999-2006 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Brody, Jane E., undated (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Brody, Lora, 1992-1999 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Broening, John, undated (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Bromberg, Eric and Bruce, 1992-2002 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Broncato, Larry, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Bronz, Ruth Adams, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Brooks, Christopher, 1998-2002 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Brown, Colin, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Brown, Doug, 1998-2003 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Brown, Ed, 1993-2003 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Brown, Ellen, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Brown, George (Dani), 1996 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Brown, George and Katie, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Brown, Graham, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Brown, Kimberly Brock, 1995-1997 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Browne, Ross, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Brownlow, Morgan, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Bruce, Daniel, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Bruce, David, 1993-2002 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Bruce, Robert, 1993-1997 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Bruel, Jean Francois, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Brunbauer, Anton, 2001-2004 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Brunacci, Frank, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Brunett, Gerard, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Brunetti, Franco, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Bruni, Stephen, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Bruno, Clemont, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Bruno, Gerardo and Antonio, 1992-2000 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Bruno, John, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Bryan, Scott (Veritas), 1993-1999 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Bryant, Valerie, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Bubala, John (Thyme), 1995 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Buben, Jeffrey, 1985-2007 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Buckner, Toman and Rozann, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Budd, Daniel, 1993-1997 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Buendia, Antonio, 1990-1998 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Buenviaje, Brenda, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Bugialli, Giuliano, 1984-1992 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Bugler, Kimberly, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Buhle, Natalie, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Bui, Minh, 1996-2000 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Buitoni, Riccardo, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Bull, David, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Bumbaris, George, undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Bundlich, Anselmo, undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Bundy, Walter E., 2000-2002 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Bunting, Tori Ritchie, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Burge, Martin, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Burgess, Tim and Vincent Derquenne, 1993-1996 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Burke, David, 1992-2007 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Burke, Jimmy, undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Burlion, Guillaume, 1994-1998 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Burns, Derek, 1992-1996 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Burrell, Anne, undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Burrows, Jonathan, 2000-2003 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Burtscher, Hans, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Buss, Brad, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Bussell, Christopher, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Busset, Thierry, undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Buster, Carolyn, 1984-2005 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Butler, Larry, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Butler, Phil, 1997-1999 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Buzzard, Terri, undated (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Butters, Rodney, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Byrnes, 1999-2004 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Cable-Larche, Dudley, undated (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Cabrera, Alberto, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Cacciola, Robert, 1994-1997 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Caceres, German, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Caiazzo, Christian, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Cairns, Michael, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Calamari, Paulo, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Calderone, Bob, 1994-1998 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Calisi, Salvatore, 2004-2005 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Calkins, Dave (Old Glory), 1992-1997 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Callahan, Brian, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Callaghan, Kenny, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Calland, Pippi, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Cam, Yannick, 1983-1995 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Camancho, Arturo Franco, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Camas, Manuel, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Cambra, Jonathan, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Cameron, Bonner, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Cameron, Stuart, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Camerota, Robert, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Campanaro, Joey, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Camanaro, Louis, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Campbell, Scott, 1990-2006 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Campbell, William, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Campbell's Soup, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Campiche, David, 1987-1992 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Campiformio, Rosemary, 1991-1995 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Canavan, Ken, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Canelle, Fabrice, 1992-1999 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Caniglia, Frank, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Cannelora, Lisa, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Cannone, Sebastien, 1995-2006 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Canora, Marco, 2001-2004 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Canteenwalla, Kim, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Cantar, Ruperto, 1995-2001 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Cantu, Homaro, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Cao, Lan Tran, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Cape, Kevin, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Cape Sea Grill, 2002-2006 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Caplan, Frieda, 1984-1994 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Capon, Josh, 2004-2005 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Capparelli, Vittorio, 1992-1998 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Cappita, Sebastiano, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Caputo, Jay, 2004-2006 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Caputo, John, 1997-2001 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Carbone, Vincent, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Cardona, Ricardo, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Cardoz, Floyd, 1998-2005 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Carey, Christopher, 2003-2008 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Cargiolli, Alessandro, 1997-2002 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Carlin, Tom, 1991-1994 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Carlucci, Joe, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Carlucci-Rodriguez, Heather, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Carman, Vesna, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Carmellini, Andrew (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Carmichael, David, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Carmouche, Bernard, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Carnier, Karen Blockman, 1988-2004 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Carpenter, Chris, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Carpenter, James, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Carrier, Karen Bockman, 1988-2004 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Carrigan, Michael, undated (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Carroll, Charles, 1989-1999 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Carsberg, Scott, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Carso, Greg, undated (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Carson, Lincoln, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Carter, Caryl, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Carter, Eric, undated (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Carter, Mark, 1985-1998 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Carter, Robert, 1985-1998 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Carthy, Andrew, undated (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Cartwright, Jonathan, 1995-2006 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Caruso, James Campbell, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Casadio, Luca, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Casale, Gregory, 2004-2005 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Casella, Cesare, 1989-2006 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Casey, Beth, 2000-2004 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Casey, Kathy, 1985-1992 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Caskey, Scott, 1995-2003 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Cashion, Ann, 1995-2003 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Cassel, Marc, 1995-1997 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Cassidy, James, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Cassino, Suzanne, undated (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Cassisi, Antonio, undated (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Castaneda, Hernan, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Castel, Alain, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Castino, Michael, 1996-1998 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Castle at Tarrytown, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Castro, Gilbert, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Castro, Giullo, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Castro, Joe, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Castro, John David, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Catherall, Tom, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Cavaiola, Georgine, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Cavallo, Shirley Maria, undated (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Cave, Terrence, 2000-2006 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Caturano, Anthony, 1997-2002 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Cawino, Michael, 2006-2008 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Cecchini, Dave, 1999-2004 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Cech, Mary, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Celentano, Albert, 1991-1996 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Celentano, Luigi, 1994-1997 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Centrello, Loren, undated (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Cerasoli, Celia, 1988-1996 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Cerbone, Ida, 1981-1999 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Cernak, Richard, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Cerra, Antonio, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Certrulo, Michael, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Chace, Kerry, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Chalermkittichai, Ian, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Challet, Jean-Pierre, 1986-2005 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Chamberlain, Richard, 1992-1997 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Chambrette, Fernand, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Chambrin, Pierre, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Champely, Franck, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Chan, Jansen, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Chan, Scott, 1988-1999 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Chandler, Rex, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Chang, David, 2006-2007 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Chang, Victor, 1987-1990 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Chappell, Christopher, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Chapelle, Don, 1995-1998 (Box 8, Folder 15a)
  - Charboneau, Regina, 1989-1994 (Box 8, Folder 15b)
  - Charest, Louis, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Charles, Rebecca, 1985-2002 (Box 8, Folder 17a)
  - Chase, Andrew, 1996-2003 (Box 8, Folder 17b)
  - Chassagne, Claude, 1994-2006 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Chauhan, Maneet, 2004-2007 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Chavanon, Dominique, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - The Chef's Garden, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Chemel, Bruno, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Chen, Fang Nan, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Chen, George Q., 1997-1999 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Chen, Richard, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Chenel, Laura, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Chenet, Joel, 1983-1998 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Cheng, Vincent, undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Cheung, Christopher, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Cheung, Henry, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Chevalier, Dany, undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Chevillard, Pierre (Chewton Glen), 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Chew, James, 1996-1998 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Chiappe, Mauro, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Chiappetti, Steve, 1995-2000 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Chiarello, Michael, 1989-2000 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Chicas, Jorge/Ghassan Jarrouj, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Child, Julia, 1989-1997 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Child, Tommy, 1993-1999 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Chillingsworth, Nitzi, undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Chin, Leeann and Katie, 2000-2002 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Chin, Philippe, 1993-2002 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Chin, Tom, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Chino, Farms, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Chirico, Vincent, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Chittum, Heather, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Chmelar, Chris, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Chodorow, Jeffrey, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Cholmondeley, Jaqueline, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Choo, Kristy, 2004-2007 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Chouvin, Andre, 1989-1992 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Chow, Philippe, 2005-2006 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Choy, Sam M.H., 1995-1997 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Christensen, Ashley, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Christensen, Stephen, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Christianson, Matt, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Chriszt, Donna, 1990-2003 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Chu, Glenn, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Chu, Lawrence, 1999-2002 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Chuah, Kelvin, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Chung, Cecilia, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Chung, Henry, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Ciao Bella Gelato, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Ciccotti, Simone, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Ciesielski, Oliver, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Cimarusti, Michael, 1991-2005 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Ciminera, Joseph, 2000-2003 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Cipollone, Chris, undated (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Cipriani, Harry, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Cirkiel, Shawn, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Ciszak, Thomas, 1997-2007 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Citrin, Josiah, 1996-2004 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Citron, Gavin, 1996-2001 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - City Harvest, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - City-Meals-on-Wheels, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Cizma, Ted, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Clare, Gerald E., undated (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Claridge, Laurann, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Clark, Dustin, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Clark, Liz, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Clark, Patrick Dean, 1990-1998 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Clark, Robert, 1997-2000 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Clark, Tony, 1996-2000 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Claude, Jean F., 2006 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Clauson, Gary, 1992-1997 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Clauss-Ehlers, Julian, 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Claussen, John, Undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Clayton, Brian, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Cleaver, Mary, 1990-1995 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Clement, Louise, Undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Clements, Brien, 2006-2007 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Clinton, Gerard, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Clogston, Francis, 1987-1993 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Close, Melissa, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Coale, Ansley J., 1993 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Cobren, James, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Cochran Jr., Joe, 1990-1994 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Cochran, John, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Coe, Frank, 2001-2003 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Cohen, Jim, 1995-2005 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Cohen, Joshua, 2000-2003 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Cohen, Scott, 1991-2006 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Cohn, Jordan, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Coladonato, Pino, undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Colamenco, Mike, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Colbin, Annemarie, 1986-1994 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Cole, Greg, 2006-2007 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Cole, Steve, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 32a)
  - Coleman, James E., 1992-1997 (Box 9, Folder 32b)
  - Coletta, John, 1993-2002 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Colicchio, Tom, 1991-2005 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Collins, Kenneth W., 2001-2003 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Colmer, John R., 1996 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Colosi, Thomas, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Colvig, Bryan, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Comess, Noel, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Comfort, Jay, 2002-2004 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Common, Craig, 1994-1997 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Conant, Scott, 2002-2005 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Concalma, Manuel, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Concannon, Patrick, 1991-1999 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Condomine, Pascal Jean, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Condron, Thomas, 2000-2002 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Conlan, Terry, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Connoly, Jim, undated (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Connolly, Millie, undate (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Connolly, Neil, 2005-2006 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Connor, Scott, 2001-2004 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Connors, Paul, 1992-2001 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Connors, Susan, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Contacessi, Raffaele, 1995-2001 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Contartesse, Maurizio, 1994-1999 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Conte, Ralph, 1993-2003 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Conte, Tony, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Conticini, Philippe, 1998-2001 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Contrisciani, Alfonso, 1997-1999 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Convertini, Massimilliano, 2004-2006 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Coohill, Tom, 1992-1995 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Cook, Sid, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Condron, Tom, 1995-2000 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Coon, Jeffrey, 1983-1995 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Cooper, Ann, 1994-2001 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Cooper, Bruce, 1993-2005 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Cooper, Ron, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Coppetti, Massimo, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Cora, Catherine, 1998-2002 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Corbett, Dean, 2005-2007 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Corea, Salvatore, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Corbin, Crystal, undated (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Cordes, Victor, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Cordua, Michael, 1988-2002 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Cormier, Alexander, 1997-1999 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Corliss, Robert, 1997-1999 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Cornaro, Pierangelo, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Cornu, Michel, 1996-2001 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Correia, Barry, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Corrigan, Richard, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Coscuella, Maurice, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Cosentino, Chris, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Constentino, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Costa, Lucie, 1991-1994 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Coston, Patrick, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Cotterman, Leslie, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Cotzomi, Ignacio, 1997-2001 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Coudouy, Pascal, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Coughenour, Keith, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Coughlin, Grant, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Courivaud, Regis, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Cousineau, Geoffrey, 1999-2002 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Covelli, Christopher, 1999-2005 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Cowley, Ian, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Cox, Gregory Ann, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Cox, Jennifer, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Cox, John, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Cox, Mark, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Coyle, Gary, 1991-2002 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Craig, David, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Crane, Steve, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Craven, Lee, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Crawford, Jeffrey, 1995-2002 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Crescenzo-Crescenzi, Francesco, 1994-2000 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Crescenzo, Maurizio and Francesco, 1994-2000 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Cressotti, Michael, 1999-2008 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Cressy, Louis, undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Crispo, Frank, 1996-2002 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Cristadoro, Sunny, undated (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Crivello, Donna, 1992-1996 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Crociani, Claudia, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Crofton, Suzy, 1995-1999 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Crosland, Jeff, undated (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Crugnale, Ercolino, 1992-1995 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Cruz-Taura, Rolando, 2000-2005 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Cuevas, John, 2003-2006 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Cuggino, Annie, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Culinary Institute of America, 1994-2002 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Culleeny, Tom, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Cullen, Kevin, 1998-2003 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Cullen, Noel, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Cullingworth, Grant, undated (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Cummings, Sean, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Cunha, Manny, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Cunningham, David, 1998-2005 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Cunningham, Marion, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Cunningham, Noel, undated (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Cunningham, Rick, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Cupani, Craig, 1997-2002 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Currence, John, 1995-2004 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Curto-Randazzo, Andrea, 1998-2003 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Curry, Robert, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Cushing, Christine, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Custer, Daniell, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Cutaneo, Scott Martin, 1996-2003 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Cuyeu, Herve, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Czapalay, Stefan, 1996-1999 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Czarnecki, Jack, 1991-2003 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Cznadel, Sean, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Dabir, Mehrdad, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Dady, Jason, 2001-2004 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Dagenback, Paul, undated (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Daguin, Andre, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Daguin, Ariane, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Dahlmann, Jens, undated (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Dahrouch, Larbi, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Dal Bon, Angelo, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Dale, Charles, 1993-2003 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Dalla Riva, Frank, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Daly, Chris, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Damanto, John Paul, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - D'Amanto, Sanford, 1988-2002 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - D'Ambruoso, David, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Les Dames d'Escoffier, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Damiano, Anthony, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - D'Amico, Andy, 1988-2004 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - D'Amico and Partners, 1987-1997 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - D'Amico, Larry, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Damidot, Eric, 2004-2006 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - D'Andrea, Peter, 1997-2002 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Dangler, Jim, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - D'Angelo, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Danhi, David, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Daniel, Peter, 1995-2005 (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Daniels, David, 2005-2006 (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Daniels, David, 1984-1996 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Danko, Gary, 1992-2004 (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Danley, William Terrell, undated (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - Dare, Russell/Demars, WIlliam, undated (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - Dargo, Jean-Paul, 2000-2002 (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Darroze, Helene, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - D'Artagnan, Inc., 1990-1998 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Das, Sumanth, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - DaSilva, Paula, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Daugherty, Seth Bixby, 2003-2005 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - DaVillion, Bruno, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - David, Elizabeth, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Davies, Ben, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Davies, Dina, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Davies, Martin, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Davies, Todd, 1995-2001 (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Davis, Ben, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Davis, Beth, 1990-1994 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Davis, Derek, 1988-1996 (Box 10, Folder 110)
  - Davis, Jerry, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 111)
  - Davis, Kevin, 1999-2003 (Box 10, Folder 112)
  - Davis, Mike, 1995-2004 (Box 10, Folder 113)
  - Davis, Mitchell, undated (Box 10, Folder 114)
  - Davis, Peter, 1995-2004 (Box 10, Folder 115)
  - Day, Bradley, 2005-2006 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Dean, Timothy, 1996-1999 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - DeAngelis, Albert, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - DeBruyn, Steven, 2002-2007 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - DeCarlo, Frank, 1996-2002 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - DeCavel, John-Robert, 1990-2005 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - DeChellis, Josh, 2003-2006 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - DeCrauzat, Serge, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Decre, Fred, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - DeFour, Tom, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Degollado, Carmen and Maria, 1995-2007 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - DeGeorgio, Michael, 2001-2006 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - DeGrezia, Joseph, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - DeGroff, Dale, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - DeJong, Peter, 1991-1995 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Delangle, Alain, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Del Bello, Alberto, 1991-1998 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - De Lessio, Patrick, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Deletrain, Franck, 1997-2007 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Del Favero, Paul, 1992-2003 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Del Grande, Robert, 1994-2003 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Delmond, Joel, 2001-2005 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Delos, Matt, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Delouvrier, Christian, 1998-2004 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Delpeuch, Danielle, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Delrieu, Georges, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Del Signore, Luciano, 2002-2004 (Box 11, Folder 27a)
  - DeLuna, Christopher, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 27b)
  - DeMagistris, Dante, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - DeMarco, Carlo, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - DeMarco, Janine, undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - DeMaria, Michael, 1997-1999 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - DeMars, William, undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - DeMasco, Karen, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Demayo, Melissa, undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - DeMedici, Lorenza, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Demers, Michael, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Demes, Anthony, 1992-1998 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - DeMonteiro, Longteine, 1991-1995 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Denaro, Franco, 1991-1994 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Dendievel, Luc, 1995-2001 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - DeNicola, Joseph, undated (Box 11, Folder 41)